<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- WelcomeActivity -->
    <string name="app_name">VisionAssist</string>
    <string name="welcome_to">Welcome to</string>
    <string name="vision_assist_logo">VisionAssist Logo</string>

    <!-- PermissionsActivity -->
    <string name="permissions">Permissions</string>
    <string name="audio_permission_warning_en">Permissions are required for the app.Please select allow, to all dialogs in the next page</string>
    <string name="audio_permission_warning_ro">Sunt necesare permisiuni pentru aplicație. Vă rugăm să selectați tot timpul, in dialogurile din urmatoarea pagina</string>
    <string name="always_allow_en">Please allow access, for correct execution of the app</string>
    <string name="always_allow_ro">Vă rugăm să permiteți accesul, pentru o funcționare corectă a aplicației</string>
    <string name="settings_open_en">Please allow access from the settings page, in the Permissions section, for correct execution of the app</string>
    <string name="settings_open_ro">Vă rugăm să permiteți accesul din pagina de setări, în secțiunea Permisiuni, pentru o funcționare corectă a aplicației</string>
    <string name="settings_button_en">Settings</string>
    <string name="settings_button_ro">Setări</string>
    <string name="camera_permission_info_en">
        The application needs camera access to help you identify objects,
        read text, and navigate your surroundings.
        This permission is essential for the app to function</string>
    <string name="camera_permission_info_ro">
        Aplicația are nevoie de acces la cameră pentru a te ajuta să identifici obiecte,
        să citești text și să navighezi în împrejurimi.
        Această permisiune este esențială pentru ca aplicația să funcționeze</string>
    <string name="storage_permission_info_en">
        The application needs storage access to save and retrieve your profile settings and preferences</string>
    <string name="storage_permission_info_ro">
        Aplicația are nevoie de acces la spațiul de stocare pentru a salva
        și a recupera setările și preferințele profilului dvs</string>
    <string name="microphone_permission_info_en">
        The application needs microphone access to enable voice
        commands for the \"Find My Objects\" feature</string>
    <string name="microphone_permission_info_ro">
        Aplicația are nevoie de acces la microfon pentru a activa comenzile vocale
        folosite de functia \"Find My Objects\"</string>
    <string name="microphone_denied_info_en">
        Without microphone access, you won\'t be able to use the \"Find My Object\" feature.
        Would you like to grant access?</string>
    <string name="microphone_denied_info_ro">
        Fără acces la microfon, nu veți putea utiliza funcția \"Find My Object\".
        Doriți să acordați acces?</string>
    <string name="give_access_en">Give Access</string>
    <string name="dont_give_en">Don\'t Give</string>
    <string name="give_access_ro">Permite acces</string>
    <string name="dont_give_ro">Nu permite acces</string>

    <!-- ConfigurationActivity -->
    <string name="problem">What is your</string>
    <string name="problem2">visual problem?</string>
    <string name="initial_blindness_notification">
        For the following setup steps, please ensure that you have the TalkBack feature enabled on your device.
    </string>
    <string name="tutorial_speak">
        Welcome to VissionAssist app,
        the sound you heard is telling you that,
        the following content that will be spoken
        could be repeated.
        By pressing volume down button once you will,
        repeat the spoken sentence at a slower rate,
        and by pressing volume down second time,
        repeat at an higher rate.
        After the spoken sentence the system will wait 2 seconds
        if you wish to repeat the sentence
    </string>
    <string name="config_activity">
        The current page is about deciding whether you want a low-eyesight or blindness profile.
        In the buttom of the page there exists 2 buttons.
        The left one is for choosing blindness profile.
        The right one is for choosing low-eyesight profile.
    </string>

    <!-- WelcomeActivity -->
    <string name="language_icon">Language selection icon</string>
    <string name="dropdown_arrow">Dropdown arrow</string>
    <string name="load_profile_info_en">
        Choose this option if you have an existing profile saved locally on your device or stored remotely in the cloud.
    </string>
    <string name="load_profile_info_ro">
        Alegeți această opțiune dacă aveți un profil existent salvat local pe dispozitiv sau stocat remote în cloud.
    </string>
    <string name="new_profile_info_en">
        Choose this option if you are new to the platform or want to create a fresh profile from scratch.
    </string>
    <string name="new_profile_info_ro">
        Alegeți această opțiune dacă sunteți nou pe platformă sau doriți să creați un profil nou de la zero.
    </string>
    <string name="load_profile_en">Load profile</string>
    <string name="load_profile_ro">Încarcă profil</string>
    <string name="new_profile_en">New profile</string>
    <string name="new_profile_ro">Creează profil</string>

    <!-- LoadProfileActivity -->
    <string name="network_miss_en">The device has no access to the internet, try to connect to a network and try again</string>
    <string name="network_miss_ro">Dispozitivul nu are acces la internet, încercați să vă conectați la o rețea și încercați din nou</string>
    <string name="account_ne_en">The email is not registered in the database</string>
    <string name="account_ne_ro">Adresa de e-mail nu este înregistrată în baza de date</string>
    <string name="generic_error_en">Error was encountered while fetching the profile</string>
    <string name="generic_error_ro">A apărut o eroare la preluarea profilului</string>


    <!-- Common values -->
    <string name="forward_arrow">Forward arrow</string>
    <string name="back_button">Back navigation button</string>
    <string name="home_button">Home navigation button</string>
    <string name="recent_apps_button">Recent apps navigation button</string>
    <string name="continue_button">Continue</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="wait_en">Please wait</string>
    <string name="wait_ro">Vă rugăm așteptați</string>
    <string name="verifying_en">Verifying profile, please wait</string>
    <string name="verifying_ro">Profilul se verifică, vă rugăm așteptați</string>
    <string name="exit_error_en">A critical error has occurred and the application needs to close to protect the integrity of your data. If this happens again, contact support with the code below</string>
    <string name="exit_error_ro">A apărut o eroare critică și aplicația trebuie închisă pentru a proteja integritatea datelor dumneavoastră. Dacă se întâmplă din nou acest lucru, contactați asistența cu codul de mai jos</string>
    <string name="temp_error_en">Device temperature is too high.The application will shut down to prevent damage</string>
    <string name="temp_error_ro">Temperatura dispozitivului este prea mare.Aplicația se va opri pentru a preveni deteriorarea</string>
    <string name="battery_low_en">Battery level is too low.Please charge your device immediately.Application will shutdown</string>
    <string name="battery_low_ro"> Nivelul bateriei este prea scăzut.Vă rugăm să încărcați dispozitivul imediat.Aplicația se va opri</string>
    <string name="critical_warning_en">Critical Warning!</string>
    <string name="critical_warning_ro">Avertisment critic!</string>
</resources>